Welcome to Path Planning.
パスプランニングへようこそ
Path planning is how the vehicle generates
パスプランニングは 目的地に到達するための安全で運転可能なトラジェクトリーを
safe drivable trajectories to get where we want it to go.
車両がどのように生成するかを考えます
We'll use data from computer vision and
周辺環境を理解するには
sensor fusion in order to understand the environment around us.
コンピュータービジョンとセンサーフュージョンからのデータを使用します
We'll also use data from localization to
さらに ローカライゼーションからのデータを使用して
understand precisely where we are in that environment.
その環境内で自分が正確にどこに位置するかを把握します
The path planning block uses all of that data to decide which maneuver to take next.
パスプランニングのブロックでは 次に取るべき動作の判断にこれらすべてのデータを使用して
Then it constructs a trajectory for the controller to execute.
その後コントローラーが実行するトラジェクトリーを作成します
In the first lesson you'll learn some of
最初のレッスンでは 離散パスプランニングで使用される
the foundational search algorithms used in discrete path planning.
基本的な検索アルゴリズムについて説明します
Then you will learn about prediction which is where we use the data from
それから予測について学習します
sensor fusion to generate predictions about
予測はセンサーフュージョンからのデータを使用して生成され
what all the other objects around us are likely to do.
自分の周辺にある他すべてのオブジェクトが実行するだろう内容について行われます
Then you'll study about behavior planning.
さらに行動プランニングも扱います
This is where we decide at a high level what
ここでは次の 10 秒くらいで車がするだろう動作を
the car shall do in the next 10 seconds or so.
ハイレベルで判断します
Finally you will learn about trajectory generation which is where we create smooth,
最後はトラジェクトリー生成について説明します モーションコントローラーが進むための
drivable, and collision-free trajectories for the motion controller to follow.
スムーズで運転可能 衝突しないトラジェクトリーを生成します
In the project at the end of this module you'll
このモジュールの最後にあるプロジェクトでは
implement a path planner for a vehicle driving on a highway.
高速道路で運転する車両のためのパスプランニングを実装します
Your vehicle will be able to avoid collisions,
車両は衝突を防ぎ
maintain safe distances between other traffic,
他の車両から安全な距離を保ち
and even pass other vehicles to get where it's going faster.
他の車両を追い越して目的地に着くまでの時間を短縮できるようになります